Quirini, Helen; Papers apap102
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Community Activism, 1898-2010; Undated; 6
  - Health Care, 1969-2009; Undated; 6.8; 4.0 cubic ft.
    - "Shaping an Affordable Health Care Future" Conference, Summary, Reports, Fliers, Articles, News Clippings, 1984 October 01 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 38)
    - Society of Patient Representatives, Correspondence, Report, 1977 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 39)
    - Upper Hudson Regional Comprehensive Planning Organization, Application for Funding, 1972 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 40)
    - Upper Hudson Regional Comprehensive Planning Organization, Correspondence, News Clippings, 1972-1973 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 41)
    - Upper Hudson Regional Comprehensive Planning Organization, Meeting Agendas and Minutes, 1975-1976 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 42)
    - Schenectady Area Comprehensive Health Planning Organization, Board of Directors, News Clippings, 1969 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 43)